[{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":164800,"timeElapsed":205179},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17915,"timeElapsed":223095},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":23049,"timeElapsed":246145},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8633,"timeElapsed":254779},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":8999,"timeElapsed":263778},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":8495,"timeElapsed":272274},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4353,"timeElapsed":276629},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4328,"timeElapsed":280959},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3559,"timeElapsed":284519},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":18505,"timeElapsed":304858},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3579,"timeElapsed":308438},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":31109,"timeElapsed":339548},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5657,"timeElapsed":345206},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6169,"timeElapsed":351376},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":354378},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4839,"timeElapsed":359218},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3805,"timeElapsed":363024},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3341,"timeElapsed":366366},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":10245,"timeElapsed":378266},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3953,"timeElapsed":382220},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7427,"timeElapsed":389648},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6317,"timeElapsed":395966},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4547,"timeElapsed":400514},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3221,"timeElapsed":403736},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3643,"timeElapsed":407380},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3139,"timeElapsed":410520},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3467,"timeElapsed":413988},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":9214,"timeElapsed":424762},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4967,"timeElapsed":429730},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5141,"timeElapsed":434872},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5169,"timeElapsed":440042},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5007,"timeElapsed":445050},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":448322},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":452366},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5991,"timeElapsed":458358},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3753,"timeElapsed":462112},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":11151,"timeElapsed":474986},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980717312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2343,"timeElapsed":477330},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5345,"timeElapsed":482676},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3025,"timeElapsed":485702},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2811,"timeElapsed":488514},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2351,"timeElapsed":490866},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5029,"timeElapsed":495896},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3667,"timeElapsed":499564},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6321,"timeElapsed":505886},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":17049,"timeElapsed":524416},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2757,"timeElapsed":527174},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2940,"timeElapsed":530115},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2685,"timeElapsed":532800},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":535494},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":538318},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2509,"timeElapsed":540828},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2863,"timeElapsed":543692},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2881,"timeElapsed":546574},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8617,"timeElapsed":556520},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1969,"timeElapsed":558490},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2793,"timeElapsed":561284},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980803908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":563926},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":566598},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2769,"timeElapsed":569368},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3173,"timeElapsed":572542},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980815092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":575110},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5045,"timeElapsed":580156},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":10913,"timeElapsed":593250},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980835584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2351,"timeElapsed":595602},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842454,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6869,"timeElapsed":602472},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9879,"timeElapsed":612352},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2913,"timeElapsed":615266},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":618268},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2219,"timeElapsed":620488},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2709,"timeElapsed":623198},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2225,"timeElapsed":625424},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980867968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2561,"timeElapsed":627986},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":12483,"timeElapsed":642184},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3005,"timeElapsed":645190},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":7239,"timeElapsed":652430},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897510,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5097,"timeElapsed":657528},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4073,"timeElapsed":661602},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980909362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":7777,"timeElapsed":669380},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980912696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3333,"timeElapsed":672714},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6097,"timeElapsed":678812},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980922442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3647,"timeElapsed":682460},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3487,"timeElapsed":685948},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16775,"timeElapsed":704112},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980948726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4631,"timeElapsed":708744},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4691,"timeElapsed":713436},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3929,"timeElapsed":717366},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980961446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4097,"timeElapsed":721464},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980964488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3042,"timeElapsed":724506},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980969944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":729962},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980973166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3221,"timeElapsed":733184},{"subjectID":"2brlgcdxkl","prolificID":"66edfefac3a39cc9aa52668a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b261353c261380cd8c6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3901,"timeElapsed":737086}]